Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - Poet files, 1969-2009; 1969-2020; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Glascar, Rayford Carter, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Goffe, Tony, 1982-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Gold, Edward, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Goldberg, Barbara, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Golden, Marita: profiles, 1988-2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Golden, Marita: "A Woman's Place", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Golden, Marita: "Migrations of the Heart", 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Golden ,Marita: "Long Distance Life", 1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Golden, Marita: promotional material, 1985-1995 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Golden, Vera, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Gonzalez, Marcial, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Gonzalez, Ray, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Goodwin, Everett: works by, 1978-1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Goss, Clay: correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Goudreau, Ron, 1992-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Graham, Jorie, 1997 July 14; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Mary Emma, 1995 August 4; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Grante, Julia, 1986-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Grafton, Michael, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Gray, Pat, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Green, Dorothy (Dottie), 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Green, Rayna, 1985-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Greenberg, Suzanne, 1990-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Greene, Michelle Calhoun, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Greenfield, Eloise: correspondence, clippings, articles, 1980-1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Gregorsen, Jeremy, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Gregory, Keith O. (Blade), Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Griffin, Jan, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Griffith, Patricia Browning, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Grimsley, Jim, 1999 November 15; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Griswold, Charles, 1985-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Grooms, Anthony, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Grooms, Anthony: correspondence, works by, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Grossman, Andrew, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Grosvenor, Vertamae, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Guess, Valerie, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Gutterman, Peter S., 1998, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Guy, Rosa, 1982-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Haarhoff, Reginald Dorian, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Hackett, Philip, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Haddis, Mekonen, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica: articles, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica: correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica: works by, cirriculum vitae, biography, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: profile, 1994-1999 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: post cards, 1983-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: flyers, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: works, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: photograph, 1986-1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Hahn, Kimiko: correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Haines, Corrie Gerald, 2006-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Haizlip, Harold and Shirlee, 1984, 1994-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Hall, Mae, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, Saskia, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Peter: correspondence (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Hammad, Suheiir, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Hammad, Suheir: post cards, 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Hammad, Suheir: correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Hammad, Suheir: poems, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Hammad, Suheir: miscellaneous, 1999-2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Hammond, Karla, 1983-1984, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Hamod, Sam: miscellaneous, 1979-2005 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Hampton, R. Kumasi, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Haney, Lynn, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Hannaham, Dawn L., 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Harer, Katherine, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Harewood, Gia L., 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Hargrave, Thomas B., 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Harjo, Joy, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Harrington, Walt, 1992, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Harris, Billy, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Harris, Iona, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Jessie, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Judith, 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Judith, 2000, 2006, 2013, 2015, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Mark P., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Harris-Ogugua, Sonya, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Harris, Ted, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Harvey, Yona, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Harvey, Yona: greetings, post cards, correspondence, articles, 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Harvey, Yona: works by, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Hass, Robert, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Hassan, Amina, 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Hausman, Gerald, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Hawkins, Gail, 1983-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Hawkins, Gary, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Hayden, Robert, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Hayden, Robert: works by, clippings, 1971-2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Hayden, Robert: flyers, clippings, profiles, 1971-2003 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Hayes III, Floyd W., 1994-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Hayes, Terrance, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Hayes, Terrance: works by, recommendation letter, 1999-2005 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Head, Bessie, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Hemphill, Essex C., 1981-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Hemphill, Essex - ENIKAlley, 2021 August; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Henderson, David, 1979, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Henderson-Holmes, Safiya, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Correspondence, 1984, 1992, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Interviews, 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Miscellaneous, 1987-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Profiles and Articles, 1973-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Promotional Material, 1993-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Reviews, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Henderson, Stephen: Works By, 1974-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 7 (1/2))
    - Henderson, Stephen: Works By, 1974-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 8 (2/2))
    - Hendrickson, Denise, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Henson, Meg, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Herndon, Daisy, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Herring, Alvin, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Herring, Amy, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Heru, Maat, 1978, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Heschel, Susannah, 1994 April 13; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Heschel, Susannah: correspondence, works by, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Hicks, Gary, 1985-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Hilal, Pima: correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Hill, Gloria Davis, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Hill, Mars, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Hillman, Mariam, 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Handprint Identity Project (H.I.P): correspondence, promotional material, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Hines, Gilbert, 1988-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Hirsch, Edward: correspondence, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Hirsch, Melissa, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Hoagland, Everett, 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Hogue, Cynthia, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Holbrook-Montgomery, Carolyn, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Holland, Christine, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Holman, Bob, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Holman, John: correspondence, promotional material and works by, 1991-1999 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Holmes, Darryl, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Hooks, Bell: letters, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Hope, Akua Lezli: correspondence, works by, 1985-1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Hopkins, James C., 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Hopkins, Lea, 1979-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Hord, Fred, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Horton, Randall, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Horton, Randall, 2010 January 25; Series 1 Subseries (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Howard, Anthony H.C., 1979, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Howard, Lee: correspondence, works by, promotional materials, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Hsu, Derrick, 1992 September 25; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Hudson, Ted, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Hughes, Langston: Articles, Reviews and Tributes (1/2), 1982-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, Langston: Articles, Reviews and Tributes, 1982-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Hughes, Langston: Notes and Lectures from a class on him, 1997-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Hughes, Langston: Memorials, Publications, and Reviews, 1978, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Hull, Gloria: promotional material, 1989-2000 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Hull, Gloria: reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Hull, Gloria: works by, 1978-1983 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Hull, Gloria: correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Hull, Gloria: miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Hunter, Delridge L., 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale, 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale - Hurston Fest '92 Program Committee, 1991-1992; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale - Hurston Fest '94 Program Committee 3/21/92 meet Miller, 1992-1994, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale - Miscellaneous, 1992, 1994, 1999, 2000, 2020, 2021 undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale - Reviews, 1977, 1979, 1980, 1992, 1994-1997, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale - Profiles & Articles, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1980, 1986-1989, 1995, 1997, 2001-2002, 2004, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Hutchins, Lorraine, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Hutchinson, Garry B., 1986-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Hylton, Patrick "Pops", Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Hyman, Amitiyah Elayne, 1992, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Hyman, Lateifa Ramona L., 1983, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Hyman, Rick, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Hypps, Irene, 1982 June 9; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Ingram, Edith, 1980-1981; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Ingrum, Adrienne, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Isaacs, Diane S., 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Iverem, Esther, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Angela, 1977, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Angela: correspondence (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Craig, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, David, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Gale, 1998; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Jackson, Hattie, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Jackson, Henry, 1982, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Jackson, Lawrence, 2002 June; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Jackson, Maurice, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Jackson, Reuben: Resume, biography, poetry, correspondence, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Reuben: clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Jacobik, Gray, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Jacobs, Bruce: correspondence, works by, 1993-1997 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Jacobs, Harriet, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs, Mary Sinclair, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - James, Cameron, 1992 March 11; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - James, C.L.R.: correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - James, C.L.R.: interviews, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - James, C.L.R.: reviews, 1983-1989 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - James, C.L.R.: obituaries, tributes, 1984-1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - James, C.L.R.: profiles, articles, 1989-1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - James, C.L.R.: promotional material, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - James, C.L.R.: works by, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - James, C.L.R.: miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - James, Kelvin, 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Jean, Valerie, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Jeffers, Lance: correspondence, poetry, 1974-1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Jefferson, Nicholas, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Jennings, Caitlin, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Jennings, Derek M., 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Jensen, Charles, n.d., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Joans, Ted: Correspondence, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Joans, Ted: correspondence, articles, 1981-1988 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Joans, Ted: Obituaries, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Joans, Ted: Works By, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Johns, Thais, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Angela, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Brandon D., 1992-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Charles, 1990, 1999, 2009, 2011, 2016; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Charles, 1997-2003, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Danny, 1992, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, Erick L., 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Helen, 1995 July 11; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, James Weldon, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Jaqueline, 1994 May; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Jocelyn, Johnson, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Linton Kwesi, 1983-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Lynelle, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Mark, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Nathaniel Jr., 1976, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Paula Camille, 1976-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Trasi: works by, correspondence, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Valerie, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Willis, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Edward: clippings, 1984-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Gayl: interview, articles, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Hargrove, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Jacquie: promotional material, works by, 1985-1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Jones, James III, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Joy A., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Joy: correspondence, articles, 1993-2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Mellenia, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Odessa, 1970, 1972, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Patricia, 1976-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Shaun, 1981-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Jones, Tosha Frances, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Venus, 2005, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, A. Van: articles, 2001-2008 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Jordan, A. Van: correspondence, programs, 1996-2006 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, A. Van: works by, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Jordan, June, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Jordan, Norman, 1973, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Jordan, Norman: correspondence, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Joselow, Beth: correspondence, promotional material, 1976-1993 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Jourdain, Rose L., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Jowers, Nzing, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Joyce, Joyce Ann, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Joyce, Joyce: works by, 1995-2004 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Joyce, Joyce: profiles, articles, 1983-1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Joyce, Joyce: correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Joyce, Joyce: promotional material, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Joyce, Joyce: miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Joyner, Carolyn: works by, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Kai, Nubia, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Karunaker, A., 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Katrak, Ketu H., 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Keene, John, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Keita, Nzadi Zimele, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Kelley, Kitty, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, Erren G., 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Patricia, 1972-1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Kenan, Randall, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Kendrick, Dolores, 2007 January 13; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Kendrick, Dolores: correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Adrienne, 1987, 1995-1996, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, Adrienne: correspondence, article, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, Ellen Conroy, 1975-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Khali, Saddi, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Khalid, Sunni, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 12 (1/4))
    - Khalid, Sunni, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 13 (2/4))
    - Khalid, Sunni, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 14 (3/4))
    - Khalid, Sunni, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 15 (4/4))
    - Khalil, Amma, 1971-1974, 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Kim, David, 1992-1995, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - King, Malcolm M., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Kitt, Sandra, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Klein, Rosemary, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Knight, Anthony, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Knight, Etheridge: correspondence, clippings, works, 1991-2002 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Knight, Hillery J., 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Kolker, Claudia, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Komunyakaa, Yusef, 1994-2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Kopperl, Helga, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard: clippings, works by, promotional material, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Kouner, Ellen Rosenberg, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Kozaitis, Anastasios, 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Kozaitis, Anastasios: correspondence, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Kreiter-Kurylo, Carolyn, 1983-1988, 1993-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Kreitzer, Jack, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Kremers, Carolyn, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Kushindana, Kwaku, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Kushnick, Louis, 1982-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Kwame (Samuel Johnson), 1983, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Laborde, Maria Rivera, 1980 May; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Ladner, Joyce, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - LaFehr, Audrey, 1993, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - LaGrone, Oliver, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Lamb, David: correspondence, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Lane, John, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Lane, Pinkie Gordon, 1986-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 4 (1/2))
    - Lane, Pinkie Gordon, 1987-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 5 (2/2))
    - Lang, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Langley, Stephen, 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Lattany, Kristin Hunter, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Lawrence, Othalene, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Lazarious, Sasha, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Leary, Robyn, 1985, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Lee, D.T., 1999-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Lee, Helen: correspondence, works by, promotinal material, 1990-1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Lee, James, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Sam, 1967, 1983-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Lee, Travis, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Leebove, Patricia Harusame, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Leeke, Madelyn, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Leftwich, David, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Lester, Julius, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, Carol, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Gina, 2005 March 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Leslie, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Naima (Gwen), Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, William Henry, 1994 December 30; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 8)